# Scofield Idehen

Delta State, Nigeria



scofield@learnhub.africa



+234 811 27 350 98



linkedin.com/in/idehen-scofield

# **Summary**

Scofield is a security expert familiar with Linux, Python, cloud computing, and blockchain.

He is good at writing research documents that can help businesses succeed.

Scofield is careful and hardworking and likes to keep things simple when solving problems.

He likes to read and work on open-source projects in his spare time. Scofield is also a technical writer for several websites, including LogRocket, Geekflare, Hackmamba, and RunX.

You can see some of his projects by visiting his page at https://scofield-idehen.github.io/home/.

# **Experience**



## **Technical Author**

LogRocket

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Support UI - Build an internal support UI template documentation for web3

Ethereum Boilerplate - A react repo with a collection of many web3 use cases

Web3UiKit -

Web3 templates - an internal project

# Technical Writer

Hackmamba

Dec 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months)

- Performing extensive research and analysis on content
- Creating specifications and content based on documentation profile
- Strategizing content pillars and sub pillars
- Collaborating with content management teams, creative teams, and writers on content documentation
- Developing editorial strategy, so content is consistent across all delivery platforms
- Conducting periodic content audits
- Strategizing and improving content delivery and promotion
- Analyzing content marketing strategy to evaluate whether it's working or not.

#### [x] Lead Technical Writer

RunX

Feb 2022 - Present (1 year)

Create Cloud Computing and Web3 Content For publications.

# LIMICORION

#### **Deputy Chief Technology Officer**

## LinkOrion Technology Ltd

Feb 2016 - Present (7 years)

- Design and build LinkOrion web projects. Including management of digital touchpoints, homepage, and landing pages
- Increase brand awareness, promote the company's products, and drive prospects to conversion
- Evaluate emerging technologies, and keep the company at the forefront of digital media.
- · Brainstorm new and creative growth strategies
- Utilize the solid analytical ability to evaluate end-to-end customer experience across multiple channels

#### **Education**



## 🕍 University of Benin

Bachelor of Arts (BA), International realation and diplomacy 2010 - 2015



## ▲ Alchemy University

Blockchain Developer, Information Technology 2022 - 2023

I recently earned a blockchain developer degree, which taught me how to design and maintain decentralized systems using blockchain technology.

Through my studies, I learned about topics such as cryptography, smart contracts, distributed ledger technology, and various programming languages and frameworks used in the development of blockchain applications.

With my blockchain developer degree, I have gained the knowledge and skills necessary to create and deploy secure, efficient, and scalable blockchain-based solutions for a variety of industries. I am also able to analyze and troubleshoot technical issues and understand the legal and ethical implications of working with blockchain technology.

Overall, my blockchain developer degree has prepared me for a successful career in this rapidly-growing field, allowing me to positively impact the world through the development of innovative and disruptive technologies.

# **Licenses & Certifications**



Advance Python Developer Course - LearnHub.Africa

#### Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner - IBM

Idehen Scofield

## **Cybersecurity Intro** - IBM

Idehen Scofield

## Identify and Investigate Cybersecurity Threats - IBM

ICSI   CNSS Certified Network Security Specialist - ICSI (Internationa
CyberSecurity Institute), UK
18594475

- Azure Administration: Identities and Governance LinkedIn
- in Planning for Azure Active Directory LinkedIn
- in Azure Administration: Deploy and Manage Compute Resources LinkedIn
- in Learning Kubernetes LinkedIn
- in Azure App Configuration LinkedIn
- in Azure Administration: Configure and Manage Virtual Networking LinkedIn
- Azure Administration: Monitor and Back Up Azure Resources LinkedIn
- Prepare for the Microsoft Azure Administrator Exam (AZ-104) LinkedIn
- in Microsoft Azure Security Technologies (AZ-500) Cert Prep: 1 Manage Identity and Access LinkedIn
- Microsoft Azure Security Technologies (AZ-500) Cert Prep: 2 Implement Platform Protection LinkedIn
- Microsoft Azure Security Technologies (AZ-500) Cert Prep: 3 Manage Security Operations LinkedIn
- Become an Azure Security Engineer LinkedIn
- **Ethereum and Solidity: The Complete Developer's Guide** Udemy UC-859f7126-5dbd-4929-beb0-755d3895f666
- Solidity Zero to Hero Course Codies Alert c606bdcae2a744a3

# **Skills**

Web Development • C++ • Solidity • Python (Programming Language) • Cloud Computing • Software Documentation • Test Automation • Test Driven Development • JavaScript • React.js

# **Honors & Awards**



# CompTia CERTMaster Learn COurse - CompTIA

Mar 2020

Learnt about Systems, Networking and security of Data, systems and Maintenance of hardware